http://www.euroncap.com/en/contact/cookie-policy/

Technical Papers
How safe is your car ?
Select one or more vehicles among the following possibilities.
Privacy Statement
How safe is your car ?
Select one or more vehicles among the following possibilities.
Cookie policy
Cookies are text files containing small amounts of information which are downloaded to your device when you visit a website. Cookies are useful because they allow a website to recognise your device, preferences and can be used to improve your online experience.
You can find more information about cookies here: https://www.aboutcookies.org/
Types of cookies we use:
Functional
Functional cookies are used to ensure you can correctly navigate our website and play videos, listen to podcasts or share pages via social media.
Performance
Performance cookies are used to analyse trends, manage the website, track visitor movements and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. Euro NCAP uses the information to compile reports and to help improve its website.  These cookies are not linked to personally identifiable information, this includes Google Analytics.
For more information about the Google Analytics cookies, click here For more information to de-activate Google Analytics cookies, click here
How to manage cookies
All recent versions of popular browsers give you a level of control over cookies.  You can set your browser to accept or reject all, or certain, cookies.  For instructions on how to manage cookies, please read the 'Help' section of your browser.  Please be aware that some areas of our website may not function after you have changed your cookie settings.
Contact
If you have any queries concerning our use of your personal information, please send a mail to privacy@euroncap.com.
June 2018
Subscribe for our latest news
OK
Euro NCAP needs your consent to process your personal data.
Please tick the following box
I agree to the use of my personal data by Euro NCAP
As a final step, you will receive an automatically generated e-mail from Paloma, our e-mail automation platform to confirm your registration.
Find our Privacy Statement here
